<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes from CHI 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chi2024-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chi2024-notes/</guid>
      <description>To be updated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/cv/</guid>
      <description>Download as PDF&#xA;Education PhD in Computer Science, University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign, 2023- Advisor: Dr. Katie Cunningham Interests: Computer science education, human-computer education BSc in Computer Engineering, Istanbul Technical University, 2018-2023 Advisor: Dr. Hazım Kemal Ekenel GPA: 3.94/4.00 Experience Research Engineer @ Vitamu | (April 2022 - June 2023)&#xA;Worked on developing learning-based algorithms for breast cancer detection and localization from digital mammography imaging. Installed training environments on cloud for computationally demanding models using Amazon Web Services (AWS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/publications/</guid>
      <description>Mehmet Arif Demirtaş, Berke Oral, Mehmet Yasin Akpınar, and Onur Deniz. Semantic Parsing of Interpage Relations. In 26th International Conference on Pattern Recognition, 2022. https://doi.org/10.1109/ICPR56361.2022.9956546&#xA;Martin Hanik, Mehmet Arif Demirtaş, Mohammed Amine Gharsallaoui, and Islem Rekik. Predicting cognitive scores with graph neural networks through sample selection learning. Brain Imaging and Behavior 16, 3 (2021), 1123–1138. https://doi.org/10.1007/s11682-021-00585-7&#xA;Alexander Waibel, Moritz Behr, Dogucan Yaman, Fevziye Irem Eyiokur, Tuan-Nam Nguyen, Carlos Mullov, Mehmet Arif Demirtas, Alperen Kantarci, Stefan Constantin, and Hazim Kemal Ekenel.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
