<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</title>
    <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://marifdemirtas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes from CHI 2024</title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/posts/chi2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/posts/chi2024/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to attend CHI 2024 in person in Honolulu, Hawaiʻi. My second in-person conference (after SIGCSE 2024 in Portland), and one of the flagship conferences of the largest ACM Special Interest Group (SIGCHI) with more than 3200 in-person participants, this was such an exciting and inspiring experience with so many amazing works and many more amazing people that I had to note down some highlights before they get lost within the pages of my notebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Curriculum Vitae (Click to Download PDF) Education PhD in Computer Science, University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign, 2023-2028 (expected) Advisor: Dr. Katie Cunningham Interests: Computer science education, human-computer education BSc in Computer Engineering, Istanbul Technical University, 2018-2023 Advisor: Dr. Hazım Kemal Ekenel GPA: 3.94/4.00 Experience AI/ML Research Intern @ ACT Inc | (June 2025 - August 2025)&#xA;Carried out a human-centered design project for identifying design opportunities for question authoring tools for subject matter experts.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Mehmet Arif Demirtaş, Claire Zheng, Max Fowler, Kathryn Cunningham. Generating Planning Feedback for Open-Ended Programming Exercises with LLMs. 26th International Conference on Artificial Intelligence in Education (AIED 2025), 2025. https://link.springer.com/chapter/10.1007/978-3-031-98417-4_3&#xA;Rafaella Sampaio de Alencar, Mehmet Arif Demirtaş, Adittya Soukarjya Saha, Yang Shi, Peter Brusilovsky. Integrating Expert Knowledge With Automated Knowledge Component Extraction for Student Modeling. 33rd ACM Conference on User Modeling, Adaptation and Personalization (UMAP 2025), 2025. https://doi.org/10.1145/3699682.3728348&#xA;Yoshee Jain*, Mehmet Arif Demirtaş*, Kathryn Cunningham.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
