<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</title>
    <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Mehmet Arif Demirtaş</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://marifdemirtas.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Notes from CHI 2024</title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/posts/chi2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 21:47:06 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/posts/chi2024/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to attend CHI 2024 in person in Honolulu, Hawaiʻi. My second in-person conference (after SIGCSE 2024 in Portland), and one of the flagship conferences of the largest ACM Special Interest Group (SIGCHI) with more than 3200 in-person participants, this was such an exciting and inspiring experience with so many amazing works and many more amazing people that I had to note down some highlights before they get lost within the pages of my notebook.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/cv/</guid>
      <description>Download as PDF&#xA;Education PhD in Computer Science, University of Illinois Urbana-Champaign, 2023- Advisor: Dr. Katie Cunningham Interests: Computer science education, human-computer education BSc in Computer Engineering, Istanbul Technical University, 2018-2023 Advisor: Dr. Hazım Kemal Ekenel GPA: 3.94/4.00 Experience Research Engineer @ Vitamu | (April 2022 - June 2023)&#xA;Worked on developing learning-based algorithms for breast cancer detection and localization from digital mammography imaging. Installed training environments on cloud for computationally demanding models using Amazon Web Services (AWS).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://marifdemirtas.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Yoshee Jain*, Mehmet Arif Demirtaş*, Kathyrn Cunningham. PLAID: Supporting Computing Instructors to Identify Domain-Specific Programming Plans at Scale. In 2025 ACM Conference on Human Factors in Computing Systems (CHI 2025), to be presented.&#xA;Mehmet Arif Demirtaş, Max Fowler, Nicole Hu, Kathyrn Cunningham. Validating, Refining, and Identifying Programming Plans Using Learning Curve Analysis on Code Writing Data. In Proceedings of the 2024 ACM Conference on International Computing Education Research - Volume 1 (ICER &amp;lsquo;24), Vol.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
